gsmarc.com 2017-12-22

# Privacy Policy - GSMArc.com

## Privacy Policy

  * Our privacy policy describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect your personal information and it is important for you to review this privacy policy.  
By "personal information" we mean information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person.
  * We do not consider anonymous information to constitute personal information as it cannot be used to identify a specific person. We collect personal information from you when you use gsmarc.com or its related websites and services ("Site") (including, without limitation, when you buy and sell items or participate in auctions or when you telephone or email our customer support team).
  * By providing us with your personal information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy.
  * We may amend our privacy policy at any time by posting a revised version on the Site.  
The revised version will be effective at the time we post it and, following such posting, your continued use of the Site will constitute your express consent to us continuing to process your personal information in accordance with the terms of our revised privacy policy.
  * We last amended our privacy policy on September 2012 and we would encourage you to check the Site regularly for the announcement of any amendments to our privacy policy.

##  **Our privacy policy covers the following topics:**

  * Our collection of your personal information
  * Our use of your personal information
  * Your use of your and other users’ personal information
  * Accessing, reviewing and amending your personal information
  * Third party website links
  * Cookies
  * No spam or spoof emails
  * Protecting your personal information
  * How you can contact us about privacy questions

##  **Our collection of your personal information**

As part of your registration on the Site, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, shipping address, email address and/or telephone number and other similar information as well as some additional information about you such as your date of birth or other identifying information.  
Additionally, in order for us to verify your identity, we may need to request from you valid proof of identification (e.g. in the form of a copy of your passport, resident’s visa or permit, national ID card and/or driver’s license).  

  * We may also collect information about your computer (for example, browser type) and navigation information (for example, the pages you visit on the Site) along with the times that you access the Site.
  * Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here.
  * We may also collect feedback ratings and other comments relating to your use of the Site.  

##  **Our use of your personal information**

We only use your personal information to provide services and customer support to you; to measure and improve our services to you; to prevent illegal activities and implement our user agreement with you ("User Agreement"); troubleshoot problems, provide you with promotional emails and verify information you give us with third parties.

We may also share your personal information with other Site members as part of an auction or "Buy Now" purchase on the Site. For example, at the end of a successful auction on the Site we will provide the seller and the successful buyer with each other’s contact information.

This contact information will be the personal information provided by you to us on registration and, as a result, should always be kept up-to-date.  
Additionally, information relating to items you are participating in displayed on the Site. This information can include details of your user ID, feedback ratings and associated comments relating to your use of the Site. Otherwise, we will only disclose your personal information to a third party with your express permission.

We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and will only share your personal information with third parties in accordance with this privacy policy.

By registering on the Site, you give us your express consent to receive promotional emails about our services and emails announcing changes to, and new features on, the Site. If, at any time, you decide that you do not wish to receive any such emails, you can opt out of receiving such emails by clicking on the link at the bottom of any of the emails or by going to the My Account section of the Site.

Additionally, we do use comments made by you about the Site for marketing purposes and by making such comments you expressly consent to our using such comments for marketing purposes.

###  **Your use of your and other users’ personal information**

Site members may need to share personal information (including financial information) with each other to complete transactions on the Site. You should respect, at all times, the privacy of other Site members.

We cannot guarantee the privacy of your personal information when you share personal information with other Site members so you should always seek information on the privacy and security policies of any other Site members with whom you are sharing any of your personal information with another Site member.

This privacy policy does not cover your release of your personal information to another Site member.

You acknowledge and agree and you shall use personal information received from another Site member in accordance with all applicable laws.

##  **Accessing, reviewing and amending your personal information**

You can access and review your personal information in the My Account section of the Site. If your personal information changes in any way or is incorrectly presented on the Site you should immediately update or correct your personal information (as applicable) by accessing the My Account section on the Site.

##  **Third party website links**

The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you when you leave the Site to read the privacy statements of each and every website you visit if you intend to provide personal information to that website. Our privacy policy applies solely to your personal information that we collect on the Site.

##  **Cookies**

Like many websites, the Site uses 'cookie' technology (small computer files placed on your computer’s hard drive). When you go to particular website pages on the Site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number.

The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us improve your experience of the Site and also help us understand which parts of the Site are the most popular. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)

##  **No spam or spoof emails**

We do not tolerate spam. To report Site related spam or spoof emails, please forward the email to. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content.

##  **Protecting your personal information**

We hold your personal information on servers located in the Canada. All personal information is encrypted. However, the Internet is not a secure medium and we cannot guarantee the privacy of your personal information. You must enter your username and password each time you want to access your account or make Reviews on the Site. Choose your password carefully using unique numbers, letters and special characters. Never share your username and password with anyone.If you are concerned that your username or password has been compromised, please immediately and ensure you change your password by logging onto the My Account section of the Site.

##  **How you can contact us about privacy questions**

If you have questions or concerns about our collection and use of your personal information, please contact our email at the bottom of the Site Privacy Policy webpage.
